(ENERGETIC MUSIC)
♪ ONE, TWO ♪
♪ ONE, TWO, THREE, OW ♪
♪ WAKE UP, KIDS WE GOT
THE DREAMERS DISEASE ♪
♪ AGE 14, THEY GOT YOU
DOWN ON YOUR KNEES ♪
♪ SO POLITE, WE'RE BUSY
STILL SAYING PLEASE ♪
♪ FRIENEMIES, WHO WHEN YOU'RE
DOWN AIN'T YOUR FRIEND ♪
♪ EVERY NIGHT I SMASH
A MERCEDES-BENZ ♪
♪ FIRST WE RUN, AND THEN
WE LAUGH 'TIL WE CRY ♪
♪ BUT WHEN THE
NIGHT IS FALLING ♪
♪ YOU CANNOT FIND
THE LIGHT (LIGHT) ♪
♪ YOU FEEL YOUR
DREAMS ARE DYING ♪
♪ HOLD TIGHT ♪
♪ YOU'VE GOT THE MUSIC IN YOU ♪
♪ DON'T LET GO, YOU'VE
GOT THE MUSIC IN YOU ♪
♪ ONE DANCE LEFT, THIS WORLD
IS GONNA PULL THROUGH ♪
♪ DON'T GIVE UP, YOU'VE
GOT A REASON TO LIVE ♪
♪ CAN'T FORGET, WE
ONLY GET WHAT WE GIVE ♪
♪ I'M COMIN' HOME, BABY ♪
♪ YOU'RE THE TOPS,
GIVE IT TO ME NOW ♪
♪ 4 AM, WE RAN A MIRACLE MILE ♪
♪ WE'RE FLAT BROKE, BUT
HEY, WE DO IT IN STYLE ♪
♪ THE BAD RICH, GOD'S
FLYING IN FOR YOUR TRIAL ♪
♪ BUT WHEN THE
NIGHT IS FALLING ♪
♪ YOU CANNOT FIND
A FRIEND (FRIEND) ♪
♪ YOU FEEL YOUR TREE
IS BREAKING JUST THEN ♪
♪ YOU'VE GOT THE MUSIC IN YOU ♪
♪ DON'T LET GO, YOU'VE
GOT THE MUSIC IN YOU ♪
♪ ONE DANCE LEFT, THIS WORLD
IS GONNA PULL THROUGH ♪
♪ DON'T GIVE UP, YOU'VE
GOT A REASON TO LIVE ♪
♪ CAN'T FORGET, WE
ONLY GET WHAT WE GIVE ♪
♪ THIS WHOLE DAMN WORLD
COULD FALL APART ♪
♪ YOU'LL BE OKAY,
FOLLOW YOUR HEART ♪
♪ YOU'RE IN HARMS WAY,
I'M RIGHT BEHIND ♪
♪ NOW SAY YOU'RE MINE ♪
♪ YOU'VE GOT THE MUSIC IN YOU ♪
♪ DON'T LET GO, YOU'VE
GOT THE MUSIC IN YOU ♪
♪ ONE DANCE LEFT, THIS WORLD
IS GONNA PULL THROUGH ♪
♪ DON'T GIVE UP, YOU'VE
GOT A REASON TO LIVE ♪
♪ CAN'T FORGET, WE
ONLY GET WHAT WE GIVE ♪
♪ DON'T LET GO, I FEEL
THE MUSIC IN YOU ♪
♪ DON'T LET GO ♪
♪ FLY ♪
♪ HIGH ♪
♪ WHAT'S REAL CAN'T DIE ♪
♪ YOU ONLY GET WHAT YOU GIVE ♪
♪ HEALTH INSURANCE,
RIP OFF LYING ♪
♪ FDA, BIG BANKERS BUYING ♪
♪ FAKE COMPUTER CRASHES DINING ♪
♪ CLONING WHILE
THEY'RE MULTIPLYING ♪
♪ FASHION SHOOTS WITH
BECK AND HANSON ♪
♪ COURTNEY LOVE AND
MARILYN MANSON ♪
♪ YOU'RE ALL FAKES,
RUN TO YOUR MANSIONS ♪
♪ COME AROUND, WE'LL
KICK YOUR ASSES ♪
♪ DON'T LET GO ♪
♪ ONE DANCE LEFT ♪